foreign
[Music]
right there come here
it is late September at the cottage and
the Wilderness surrounding me is
plunging in the full Autumn the willow
leaves are turning to deep gold the
Huckleberry bushes the bright crimson
and I find myself sporting a red nose as
the morning chill tickles my face
[Music]
today I needed to stop by my local shop
to refill some of my empty toiletry
containers and buy simple grains and tea
I'm on a tight budget this season as
we're trying to put money aside for
starting a family in the new year and
due to this I can't afford to go over
budget to partake in the flurry of
autumn shopping
foreign
[Music]
this month the stores get packed full of
all types of decorations and they're
quite enchanting autumn in my country
feels like much more than a natural
occurrence it is a shopping season Above
All Else however it is not really an
option for me to buy a lot of seasonal
things apart from restocking my pantry
with some orange spiced tea and picking
up a new Autumn candle something warm to
drink and a book to feel cozy for fall
of course I will be buying some treats
but I'm doing my best to only purchase
Essentials and Be Frugal where possible
I've always lived simply but right now
every little bit counts and it has
actually been a really wonderful
practice to make as few unnecessary
purchases as possible
most of the decorations in my home have
been borrowed from nature with plans to
return them for composting in the New
Year if I really want to decorate with
something less compostable I will be
gravitating to thrift stores to reuse
and repurpose older items
[Music]
these practices got me thinking about
how I can best celebrate Autumn and it
occurred to me that if you truly and
deeply love a season so much if it fills
you with all those cozy feelings then I
can't think of a better way to honor
this gift from nature than giving it
some love back by choosing Simplicity
and sustainability when possible
foreign
[Music]
and if you get the chance to go outside
and let the autumnal weather fill you
with wonder if you don't happen to live
in an area that has an Autumn season
this is simply a chance to learn about
your local natural world even in the
busiest cities nature still exists and
is just a little more hidden waiting to
be noticed
[Music]
in this way I like to think I'm doing my
part in preserving the future of autumn
itself and to say thank you to the
beauty anyway this is just what I'm up
to this week you will certainly see
these new practices reflected in my
channel because I will be trying to
reuse things a lot this autumn and
winter perhaps it won't be as exciting
but hopefully it inspires you to find
unique ways to enjoy each season with
simplicity
I find it helps my mind feel more
peaceful as well it's a practice that
becomes imbued in all aspects of my life
[Music]
hmm
there is nothing like the taste of cider
in early fall when it's just starting to
get more chilled it is
so delicious I am officially in the in
between Time of the Season when it is
just a little bit too cold to wear short
sleeves but it is also too warm to wear
a sweater and I keep changing in and out
of this so hopefully it will the weather
will kind of decide what it's going to
be soon enough as I said in this video I
will be trying to find ways to enjoy the
Autumn season through keeping a
realistic sustainability and simplicity
in mind which is uh not always easy I
totally understand everything in the
stores right now is so fun to look at
and and it's just such a lovely season
but due to being on a very tight budget
this year due to planning a lot of
changes in the future and trying to save
for that I realized that you know I do
think the best way to honor a season is
to really keep the nature in mind and
think about ways that we can live a
little more simply and enjoy a season
for what it is Autumn is certainly a
state of mind it is not about the amount
of things you have and no one should
ever feel any pressure to buy autumnal
items when autumn is already all around
us if it is not Autumn where you live or
if you happen to live in a quite urban
area or in a city I will leave some
recommendations down below of books that
all talk about
discovering the hidden natural world all
around you no matter what environment
you're in I cannot remember the title
but I will leave a picture here it is a
really lovely book that talks all about
the ecosystems and the ways that nature
exists within cities and it is
fascinating and it's beautiful and it
will just open up the Wonder of your
home so over the next couple months
you'll be seeing a lot of autumnal
celebrations that will be very budget
focused and cost friendly because that
is where I personally am right now I of
course will be purchasing some quite
necessary treats in my opinion for the
autumn season one is I always get an
Autumn themed candle of course I tend to
look for a new book related to the
Autumn or seasonal living or I get it
from my library however you will see
some new candles that is for sure I can
hear my bunnies causing an absolute
Ruckus upstairs so I'm gonna go check on
them and then I'm gonna take my dog Iger
out for a beautiful nature walk there's
a specific Trail we like to go on in the
Autumn because all the trees have left
their leaves on the ground and it is so
beautiful it is all golden and red tones
so we're gonna go enjoy that and I'm
gonna take you along because it is way
too special of a place not to share
sending you so much love and I will see
you soon
time a fairy who had somehow gotten into
Mischief was condemned by the high court
of Fairyland to live for several years
under the form of some creature resuming
her natural appearance once again to
make the fortune
foreign
[Music]
thank you